We've looked at the node interface and the element interface,
我们查看了 Node 接口和 Element 接口
but there are just so many more interfaces.
但实际上还有无数的接口
Just think about the anchor element or a heading element,
例如链接元素或标题元素
each one of these is backed by its own interface with properties and methods.
这些元素也都由自己的接口提供支持 同样具有属性和方法
To see a list of all of these interfaces,
要查看所有这些接口的列表
let's check out the web APIs page.
我们打开 Web API 页面
Now, we can scroll down a little bit over here and in the N category, we'll find node.
稍微向下滚动一下 在 N 类别中可以找到 Node
And we can scroll down a bit more and on
再向下滚动一下
the left-hand side of page we can find the element interface.
在页面左侧可以找到 Element 接口
Let's take a look at this interface up here.
我们在上面看看这个接口
Where is HTML? Here we go.
HTML 在哪里? 找到了
HTML element, let's look at this interface.
HTMLElement 我们来看看这个接口
Now, in this interface we can see that it inherits from element,
可以看到这个接口继承自 Element
which inherits from node.
Element 又继承自 Node
So every single HTML element will inherit these properties and methods.
所以每个 HTMLElement 都将继承这些属性和方法
And this HTML element interface has its own properties and methods.
这个 HTMLElement 接口具有自己的属性和方法
Now going back to the list of all of them,
回到所有接口列表
let's look at something specific like the anchor element right here.
我们看看某个具体的接口 例如这个 HTMLAnchorElement
So the anchor element inherits from the HTML element.
HTMLAnchorElement 继承自 HTMLElement
Going back, let's see is there a video?
回到该页面 看看是否有视频
There's got to be an HTML video tag.
应该有一个 HTMLVideo 标签
Let's scroll to the bottom here.
滚动到底部
And here's HTML video element interface.
这是 HTMLVideoElement 接口
And this inherits from HTML media element,
这个接口继承自 HTMLMediaElement
which inherits from the HTML element,
HTMLMediaElement 继承自 HTMLElement
which inherits from element and node.
HTMLElement 继承自 Element 后者继承自 Node
And this HTML video element interface gives us
这个 HTMLVideoElement 接口
the properties and methods for every single video tag.
为每个 video 标签提供了属性和方法
So there are really a ton of
总的来说 这里有无数的接口
different interfaces with a lot of different properties and methods.
并且它们都具有无数的不同属性和方法
So, you should definitely check out this page.
强烈建议你查看此文档页面